Guide to the Physics Department records, 1930-2005 RG0077
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Office records (2011.065 accretion), 1967-2005; Series 7; George Washington University. Dept. of Physics; 3 Linear Feet
  - Giant Resonance in Deformed Nuclei:Photoneutron Cross sections for Eu153, Gd169, Ho165 and W186, 1969; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Detection of NonResonant Neutron Capture in Pb207 via the Threshold Photoneutron cross section for Pb208, 1969; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Correlation Between Neutron and Gamma-Ray Widths for Fine Structure of the "Doorway" State in 207Pb, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Photoneutron Cross Sections for Sn116, Sn117, Sn118, Sn119, Sn120, Sn124 and Indium, 1969; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Threshold Photoneutron Cross Section for Mg25 and Isobaric Analogs of Na25, 1970; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Three-Body Photodisintergration of he3, 1970; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - A new detector for KeV Neutrons, 1970; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Photoneutron Cross Section for He4, 1970; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - M1 Giant Resonance in 208Pb from Threshold Photoneutron Measurements, 1970; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Photoneutron Cross Sections for Ba138 and N14, 1970; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Threshold Photoneutrons and Photon Doorways, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Threshold Photoneutron Cross Sections for 206, 207, 208 Pb, 56, 57Fe, 52,53Cr, 24, 25, 26Mg, and 19F, 1971; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Evidence for Doorway States in 207Pb, 208Pb, and 57Fe from Threshold Photoneutron Cross Section Measurements, 1971; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Photoneutron Cross Sections for 24Mg, 26Mg, and Natural Magnesium, 1971; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Phtoneutrons Spectra from Monochromatic Annihilation Radiation, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Statistical Properties of Nuclei-Threshold Photoneutrons and Photon Doorways, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Photoneutron Cross Section for 4He up to 31 MeV, 1971; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Photoneutron Cross Sections for 23Na and 25Me, 1971; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Photodisintergration of the Alpha Particle-A testing ground for charge symmetry, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Concerning the Question of Non-resonant neutron capture in 207Ph, 1972; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Precison Measurement of T=3/2 states in 25MG using the Threshold Photoneutron Technique, 1972; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Atlas of Photoneutron Cross Sections obtained with monoenergetic photons, 1973; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Systematic Properties of the Giant Resonance:Current Status, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Photoneutron Cross Sections For 7Li, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - The Livermore Photoneutron cross Section Experiement, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Kerman Quang Analysis of Giant Resonance Data, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Mass Variation of the Nuclear Symmetry Energy, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Recent High-Resolution(y,n) measurements at Livermore, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - VIII.A Photonuclear Reactions, 1974; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Photoneutron cross sections of 58Ni and 60Ni, 1974; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Three-body photodisintergration of 3He, 1974; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Atlas of Photoneutron Cross sections obtained with monoenergetic photons, 1975; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Measurements of the giant dipole resonance with monoenergetic photons, 1975; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Photoproton cross section for 18O as a measure of the effect of the Valence Neutron on the 16O Core, 1976; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Atlas of the Photoneutron cross sections obtained with monoenergetic photons, 1976; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Isopin shift of the Energy of the Giant Resonance, 1977; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Measurement of the 4He (y, p)-to-(y,n) cross-section ratio, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Photoneutron Cross sections for 13C, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Intermediate Energy Proton Scattering from oxygen-16, 17, 18 Abstract Submission, 1978; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - The Photoneutron Reaction in17O:Ground-State Differential Cross Section and 98*, 1978; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Electron Scattering from the Ground-State magnetization Distribution of 17O, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Total Photoneutron cross section for 17O, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Photonuclear Cross Sections for 180, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Photoneutron cross sections for 55Mn and 59Co, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Giant Resonance in Transitional Nuclei:Photoneutron cross sections for osium isotopes, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Experimental Determination of Photofission Neutron Multiplicities for 235U, 236U, 238U, and 232Th using monoenergetic photons, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - The Giant Resonace for the Actinide Nuclei: Photoneutron and Photofission for Cross sections for 235U, 236U, 238U and 232Th, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Determination of the Giant E2 Isoscalar Resonance for 236U, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Giant Resonances in the Photofission of Uranium even Isotopes, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Channeling Radiation from Positrons, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Observation of Radiation from Channeled Positrons, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Photofission and Electrofission, 1978; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Giant Resonance in Transitional Nuclei:Photoneutron cross sections for osium isotopes, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Precise Measurement of the charge-distribution differences of the oxygen isotopes, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Photonuclear cross sections for 180, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Photonuclear cross sections for 13C, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - 4He(y,p)-to-(y,n) to cross section ratio, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Photoneutron reaction in 170:Ground-state differential cross section, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Photoneutron cross sections for 55Mn and 59Co, 1979 July; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Observation of Channeling Radiation from Relativistic Electrons, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Precise Measurement of the charge-distribution differences of the oxygen isotopes, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Determination of the Giant E2 Isoscalar Resonance for 236U, 1979; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Photoneutron cross sections for 170, 1980; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Neutron total cross section for tritium, 1980; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Test of E2 virtual-photon distorted wave Born Approximation, 1980; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - E2 giant resonances and an M1 component in the photofission of 236U, 1980; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Photoneutron cross-section for 4He, 1980; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Photodisintergration of 3H, 1980; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Signratures of Density Dependence in the Two-Nuclear Effective Interaction near 150 MeV, 1980; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Study of Electrofission Hadron induce Fission decay and the giant quadropole resonance of 238U, 1980; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - The Neutron zero-energry total cross section and scattering lengths for tritium, 1980; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - A measurement of the 180 photonuclear cross sections as a test of Bremsstrahlung unfolding technique, 1980; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Neutron-capture cross sections for osmium isotopes and the age of the universe, 1981; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Fission decay of the giant quadrupole resonance for 234U, 1981; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Photodisintergration of 3H and 3He, 1981; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Electromagnetic dissociation of relativistic 18O Nuclei, 1981; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Photoneutron cross section of 29Si, 1981; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Observation of radiation from ?n=3 transitions for planar channeled electrons, 1981; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Transfer of 14C Target Material from LANL Target Cells to LLNL Target Cells, 1982; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Intergrated Photonuclear Cross Section for 16O, 1981; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Electromagnetic Dissociation of relativistic heavy ions:A Photon Target*, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - The Chadwick Nucleon Polarimeter, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Pion Single Charge Exchange on the A=3 Nuclei, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Ground-state Rotational-Band Transitions in 21Ne and 23Na, 1989; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Vector-Meson Decay of High-Lying Nucleon Resonances, 1989; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Simultaneous Measurements of the Electric and Magnetic Form Factors of Bound Nucleons, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - The Reactions 3He(e, e'pn) and 4He(e,e'pn) in the Region Beyond Quasi-Elastic Scattering, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Electroexcitation of 6- states in 32s (update), 1987; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Large-Angle Protons from Neutron Bombardment of Carbon, 1992; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Medium effects on the (e, e'n) reaction, 1991; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Elastic Pion Scattering from 3H and 3He in the region of the ?(1232) Resonance, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - p+ and p- elastic scattering on Tritium and 3He around 78*, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Inelastic Electron Scattering to Jp=4- and 6-states in 18O, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - The Distribution of M6 Strengthn in 30Si and 32S: A Stepping Stone to Understanding the Fragmentation of Stretched Strength in Nuclei, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Study of Pion-Nucleus elastic scattering at energies above the ? Resonance, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Atlas of Photoneutron Cross Sections Obtained with Monoenergetic Photons Final Edition, 1986; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Implications of the experimental results on the photodisintergration of 4He, 1983; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - Neutron Total Cross section for Tritium obtained from p-3He Scattering, 1980; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Electron and Positron Channeling Radiation from Type-Ia and Type-Iia Diamonds, 1984; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Channeling-Radiation Measurements at Lawerence Livermore National Laboratory, 1985; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - Positron Beams at CEBAF, 1984; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - Planar Channeling Radiation from Relativisitic Positrons and Electrons in LiF, 1984; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - Electromagnetic Dissociation of Radioactive Heavy-Ion Beams, 1984; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Coherent Bremstrahlung Produced by Relativistic Positrons and Electrons on a Single Crystal of Silicon, 1974; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Channeling Radiation from LiH and LiD, 1995; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - Crystal Properties from Channeling-Radiation Measurements, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - Channeling Radiation Past Achievements and Future Prospects, 1991; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - Applications of Channeling Radiation, 1993; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - A monoenergetic xray system for cardiovascular imaging based on bremsstrahlung, 1994; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - Intensity dependent electron beam energy losses in oriented single crystal, 2000; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Development of Monochromatic x-ray Sources with Controllable Spectral and Angular Characteristics, 2000; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Channeling Radiation: A historical perspective, 2000; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Transition Radiation as an X-ray source, 1983; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Evaluation of X-ray Detectors, undated; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Measurement of the Properties of Transition Radiation From Medium Energy Electrons, 1985; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Channeling Radiation from GeV Electrons in Diamond, undated; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - MsC 782, undated; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Temperature Dependence of Planar Channeling Radiation, 1987; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Electron and positron channeling radiation from beryllium oxide, 1993; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Thermal-vibrational amplitudes of silicon determined by channeling-radiation measurements, 1991; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Measurement of the occupation lengths of channeled 17-MeV electrons and 54-MeV electrons and positrons in silicon by menas of channeling radiation, 1989; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Channeling Radiation from LiH, undated; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Planar channeling radiation from 54-110-MeV electrons in diamond and silicon, 1988; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Proposal to the Bates Linear Accelerator Center:The Application of Transition Radiation to Non-invasive Angiography, 1986; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Relativistic Channeling Workshop, 1986; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Channeling Radiation and Related Studies Using Electron Beams from the NIST Race-Track Microtron, undated; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Planar Channeling Radiation from Silicon, 1985; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Coherent Radiation Sources, 1984; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Positron and Electronn Channeling Radiation from LiF, 1983; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Occupation lengths of bound states in electron planar channeling determined by channeling radiaton, undated; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Sharp-Line and Broad Continuum Radiation from Electrons Channeled in Diamond, 1981; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Electron and Positron planar channeling radiation from diamond, 1983; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Workshop on Detectors for the CLAS Photon Tagger, 1989; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Photoproduction measurements at CEBAF, 1991; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Report of the NSAC Ad Hoc Subcommittee on a 4 GeV CW Electron Accelerator for Nuclear Physics, 1984; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 1985 CEBAF Summer Workshop Poster, Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - SURA Newsletter February, 1984; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - SURA Newsletter July, 1984; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - SURA Newsletter September, 1984; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - SURA Newsletter November, 1984; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - SURA Newsletter April, 1984; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - CEBAF Summer Workshop Notes, 1985; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - CEBAF meeting notes, 1984; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Coincidence Measurements from Nuclei, 1987; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - SURA Newsletter March, 1985; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - SURA Newsletter April 1985, Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - SURA Newsletter July 1985, Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - SURA Newsletter September 1985, Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - SURA Newsletter April 1986, Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - SURA Newsletter May 1987, Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Review of the 1983 Long Range Plan for Nuclear Science, 1984; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Positrons at CEBAF! Positron Working Group Report, undated; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - The JLAB Coherent Bremsstrahlung Facility: A Status Report, 1998; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - A linearly-polarized photon facility based on coherent bremsstrahlung, undated; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Reaction 6Li 9(e,e'd) and 4He and the a-d Momentum Distribution in the Ground State of 6Li, 1986; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - A study of the 6Li(e,e'3H)3He and 6Li(e, e'3He)3 reactions, 1987; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Trinucleon cluster knockout from 6Li, 1998; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Memorandum of understanding between the George Washington University and the Continuous Electron Beam Accelerator Facility, undated; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Continuous Electron Beam Accelerator Facility Outline of Intentions, 1994; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Production of Vector Mesons with Monoenergetic Photons, 1987; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Photoproduction of the po in Few-Body Nuclei, 1989; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - A Coherent Bremsstrahlung Facility for TJNAF, undated; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Memorandum outlining the development of channeling radiation, 1991; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Acquisition and Renovation of GMU Racetrack Microtron, 1992; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Jury Proposal on mine detection, 2000; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Reviewer's Report on ISTC Proposal by M.I. Melnik et. Al, 2005; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Reviewer's Report on DOE Proposal by B. Vlahovic "A Pair Polarimeter for Linearly Polarized High-Energy Photons", 2005; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Referee's Report on S. Muller et. Al 187Re(y,n) Cross Section close to and above the Neutron Threshold, 2005; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Referee's Report on J.D.T. Arruda-Neto et al. The role of transitional levels in 237 Np(y, f)-perspectives to study highly deformed systems, 2005; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Reviewer's Report on ISF Research Grant Application by E. Piasetzky, "Hard Photodisintergration of a Proton Pair", 2004; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Referee's Report on V.B. Ganenko et al. Simulation of Coherent Radiation by GeV Electrons in Oriented Crystals, 2004; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Moldovan BGP Final Reviewer Report for Proposal 7375, 2003; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Reviewer's Report on ISTC Proposal 2711, "Measurement of Neutron Induced Fission Cross Sections for.." by L.A. Vaishnene et al., 2003; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Referee's Report of Nuclear photofisslity of narPb at energies above the pion photoproduction threshold, 2003; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Referee's Report on Super Interesting Heresies, 2003; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Referee's Report on R.A. Carrigan et al. Electron Channeling Radiation Experiments at Very High Electron Bunch Charges, 2003; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Reviewer's Report on ISTC Proposal 2637 "Developing the Experimental Model+22 More words", 2003; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Referee's Report on O.A.P. Tavares et al., Nuclear Photofissility of natPb at Energies above the Pion Photoproduction Threshold, 2003; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Reviewer's Report on DOE Proposal, "Radiative Capture and Gamma-Induced Reactions at Low Energies", 2003; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Reviewer's Report on Theoretical Investigations of Photofission Processes for Heavy Nuclei Detection in Large Volumes, 2002; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Referee's Report on M. Chiba et al., 200-MeV Bremsstrahlung Tagged Photon Beams at Sendai, 2002; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Referee's Report on T.E. Rodrigues et al., "Statistical and Direct Aspects of 64Zn(y,n) and (y,np) Decay Channels in the GDR and QD Energy Regions", 2002; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Referee's Report on S. Kahane et al., Elastic and Raman Scattering from Au, Dy and In of 9.0 and 11.4-MeV Photons, 2002; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Referee's Second Report on L.N.S. Prakash Goteti et al. "Dechanneling of Electrons by Stacking Faults: A Quantum Mechanical Calculation", 2001; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Referee B's Second Report for Pietralla et al. "Parity Measurements of Nuclear Levels Using an FEL Generated y-ray Beam", 2001; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Review of Nuclear and Subnuclear Physics by C.W. Wong, undated; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - CRDF Science Centers Proposal Evaluation:Neutron Induced Fission Cross Sections of Pu-240, Am-243 and W in the Energy Range 1 200 MeV, 2001; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Report for Manuscript:CF2312 "Photoneutron Cross Section" by E. Wolynec et al, undated; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Referee's Second Report for Ms. CJ10053, "Photoneutron Cross-Section Measurements on the N=82 Nuclei" by H Utsunmiya et al., 2005; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Reviewer's Third Report on S. Muller et al., "187 Re(y,n) Cross Section close to and above the Neutron Threshold", 2005; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Referee's Report on K.W. Wenzel, "Photonuclear Reactions for Simulating Radiation Damage in Nuclear Waste Forms", 1998; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Referee's Report on M.L. Terranova et al. "Photofission Cross Section and Fissility of Pre-Actinide and Intermediate-Mass Nuclei by 120- and 145-Mev Compton Backscattered Photons", 1997; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Referee's Report for Ms. LZ2147, "Excited-State Giant Dipole Resonances in (p,y)" by D.H. Dowell et al., 1983; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Departmental Files, 1969-2009; Series 8; 0.75 Linear Feet 1 partially-filled record center carton (Box 1)
  Files covering department administrative matters such as the evolution of the department's graduate programs, the creation and recruitment for new faculty positions, announcements, and departmental meetings. Also includes a file on the university-wide Information Technology Advisory Council, 1998-1999.
  These files contain confidential employee and faculty information, and must be reviewed by an archivist prior to use by researchers.
  Accession 2017-039
- Faculty records, 1930-1995; Series 9; 3.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains documents from Professors William Parke and Raymond Seeger. The material includes research, published works by Parke and Seeger, course material, Sigma Xi documents, and papers from other physicists. The material dates between 1930-1995.
  This series is arranged chronollogically.
  - Publications by Raymond Seeger, 1930-1975; Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Luther Club, 1931-1938; Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Our Physical Heritage - Seeger, 1935; Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - International Encyclopedia of Unified Science, 1938-1951; Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ten Lectures on Science, 1939; Series 9 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Physical Review, 1940-1942; Series 9 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Naval Ordnance Lab, 1943-1984; Series 9 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bessel - binder, 1943-1979; Series 9 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Professor Jehle, 1946-1983; Series 9 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Kirkwood Statistical Mechanics, 1947; Series 9 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Theodore von Karman "Aerodynamics", 1947; Series 9 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Theodore von Karman "Theory of Turbulence", 1948; Series 9 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Various publications, 1948; Series 9 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Various publications, 1955-1969; Series 9 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Publications by Professor Seeger, 1959; Series 9 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Publications by Raymond Seeger, 1956-1977; Series 9 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Thermodynamics reprints, 1956-1966; Series 9 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Naval Ordnance Laboratory - Seeger, 1959; Series 9 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Seeger publications, 1964-1974; Series 9 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "On Galileo's philosophy of science in retrospect", 1964; Series 9 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - William C. Parke papers, 1964-1967; Series 9 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - B. Decay notes part 1, 1968; Series 9 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - B. Decay notes part 2, 1968; Series 9 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Material sent to Professor Parke, 1969-1983; Series 9 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Three neutron system, 1970; Series 9 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Astronomy, 1971; Series 9 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Course proposals, 1971-1973; Series 9 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Course papers, 1972; Series 9 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Notes, 1972; Series 9 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Angular referendce, 1973-1989; Series 9 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Story of Sigma Xi, 1974; Series 9 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Companions in Zealous Research, 1976; Series 9 (Box 5, Folder 8)